sbismart.com 2019-12-10

# 

                                       PRIVACY POLICY
Approved by the Board of Directors on 15th January, 2019

                                                  CONTENTS
  1.  Introduction .............................................................................................................. 3
  2.  Collection of Information ......................................................................................... 3
  3.  What PII is collected from you? ............................................................................... 3
  4.  Use and disclosure of Personal & Financial Information ...................................... 4
  5.  For How long do we need your data ....................................................................... 4
  6.  Reasonable Security Practices for Protecting Information ................................... 4
  7.  Procedure to Safeguard Information....................................................................... 5
  8.  Changes to the Privacy Policy ................................................................................ 5
  9.  Disclaimer as to Loss............................................................................................... 5
  10. Non-Binding .............................................................................................................. 5
  11. How to Contact us .................................................................................................... 5
Approved by the Board of Directors on 15th January, 2019

   Privacy Policy
   1. Introduction
      A warm welcome to you from SBICAP Securities Limited. The domain name
      www.sbismart.com is owned by SBICAP Securities Limited only.
      The term "You" or "User" shall mean any natural or legitimate individual including
      online/offline customers/users and the terms "We", "Us", "Our" shall mean SBICAP
      Securities Limited.
      We understand that our customers and website visitors are concerned about the privacy
      of information. We are dedicated to safeguard all the sensitive information that you share
      with us.
      The policy sets forth various security practices and procedures that shall apply to the use
      and disclosure and sharing of sensitive personal data or information, Personally
      Identifiable Information (‘PII’) provided by the registered users of the website.
   2. Collection of Information
      We understand clearly that you and your Personal Information is one of our most valuable
      assets. We store and process your Information including any Personally Identifiable
      Information ‘PII’ collected, if any, on computers that may be protected by physical as well
      as reasonable technological security measures and procedures in accordance with
      regulatory authorities.
      We acknowledge and accept that the personal details that you impart to us, is to be kept
      in strict confidentiality and to use the information only in the manner which would be
      beneficial to our customers. We consider our relationship with you as invaluable and
      strive to respect and safeguard your right to privacy. We shall protect the personal details
      received from you with the same degree of care, to prevent the unauthorized use,
      dissemination, or publication of these information as we protect our own confidential
      information of a like nature.
      We shall use the personal information to improve our service to you and to keep you
      updated about our new product or information that may be of interest to you. The
      information collected from you would be used in the right spirit and context in which it is
      intended to be used.
3.    What PII is collected from you?
      Website would require registration, when registering or giving feedback on our site, you
      may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, feedback or other
      details to help you with your experience.
      We collect IP addresses for site security and to better understand of how our visitors use
      our site so that we can improve our site and your experience.
      In addition, we use small bits of data called cookies stored on user's computers to
      stimulate a continuous connection. Please visit out Cookies Policy for more details.
                                                                                      Page 3 of 5

Privacy Policy
4. Use and disclosure of Personal & Financial Information
   We would also impart your personal information wherever it is required to be disclosed
   under law to any of the governmental agency or regulatory authorities. By agreeing to
   avail the services offered by us, you have agreed to the collection and use of your
   Sensitive Personal Data or Information.
   You have the right to refuse or withdraw your consent to share/dissemination of your
   Sensitive Personal Data or Information. However, in such an event, you would no longer
   avail the services offered by us.
   Also, under certain situations, we may be required to share the information given by you
   with the third parties retailers, where we think that they can bestow to build on adding
   more value and upgrade the quality of services communicated by us to you. We shall
   take all appropriate steps to ensure that the confidentiality of your information is
   maintained by imposing strict privileged standards on all the third parties with whom we
   part this data with.
   We will share your personal data within our group of companies and with authorised third
   parties. This is necessary to place, administer your investments and our business and
   employees and to check on your suitability for our products and services. Third parties
   that we may share your data with include:
    − Lenders
    − Regulators
    − Sub consultants
    − Other intermediaries
   However, these parties would be required to use the information obtained from us for
   such purposes exclusively. We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to ensure that
   the confidentiality of your information is maintained.
5. For how long do we need your data
    We will only retain personal data for as long as necessary and as required by different
    Statutes, for the purposes for which it was gained and where we continue to have a
    lawful basis for doing so. If the personal data is no longer necessary, or where we no
    longer have the lawful basis for processing we may delete or fully anonymise the data.
    The retaining of data is necessary where required for contractual, legal or regulatory
    purposes or for our legitimate business interests and marketing purposes. Sometimes
    we may need to retain your data for longer, for example if we are defending ourselves in
    a legal dispute or as required by law or where evidence exists that a future complaint
    may occur.
6. Reasonable Security Practices for Protecting Information
   We use various types of technical safeguards in order to maintain the confidentiality and
   integrity of your personal information. Once we receive your transmission of information,
   we make commercially rational efforts to shield the security of our network.
                                                                                Page 4 of 5

 Privacy Policy
    For protection of your privacy and security, we take feasible measures to verify your
    identity before permitting you access to your account. The user shall be responsible for
    maintaining the secrecy of their entire account information.
7. Procedure to Safeguard Information
    Your personal information is stored in secured networks and only limited number of
    persons can access your personal information. These personnel are conferred special
    access rights and are required to keep the information confidential. All sensitive/credit
    information you provide is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
    Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in
    order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. In order to ensure your PII is safe
    with us, we undertake a variety of security measures when you enter your transaction
    details, submit, or access your information.
    To fortify security of access to the personal information and transaction details, the
    access to the secured zone of our website is restricted by the unique login ID and
    Password selected by you. You should be very cautious in handling the ID and password
    and you should ensure that you do not reveal it to anybody, nor do you keep it in writing.
8. Changes to the Privacy Policy
    From time to time, SBICAP Securities Limited may update or refurbish this privacy policy.
    If there are adjustments to the terms of this privacy policy, documents containing the
    revised policy on the website will be updated.
9. Disclaimer as to Loss
    Although, suitable steps are taken to maintain the security of Personal Information we
    gather from you. Under no circumstances shall SBICAP Securities Limited be liable to
    you or any other third parties for any loss or damage (including, without limitation,
    damage for loss of business or loss of profits) arising directly or indirectly from your use of
    or inability to use, this site or any of the material contained in it. SBICAP Securities
    Limited assumes no responsibility for any false, inaccurate, inappropriate or incomplete
    information presented on the website.
 10.     Non-Binding
    Please note that this privacy policy does not create any contractual or other legal rights in
    or on behalf of any party, nor is it intended to do so.
 11.      How to Contact us
         If you have any questions,               please    contact   us     by   emailing    to  :
         helpdesk@sbicapsec.com
                                                                                      Page 5 of 5
